question_data=[
    {
      "category": "Science & Nature",
      "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "Igneous rocks are formed by excessive heat and pressure.",
      "correct_answer": "False",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "True"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Entertainment: Film",
      "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "Leonardo DiCaprio won an Oscar for Best Actor in 2004&#039;s &quot;The Aviator&quot;.",
      "correct_answer": "False",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "True"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Sports",
      "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "Peyton Manning retired after winning Super Bowl XLIX.",
      "correct_answer": "False",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "True"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
      "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "&quot;Half-Life 2&quot; runs on the Source Engine.",
      "correct_answer": "True",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "False"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
      "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "In &quot;Super Mario Bros.&quot;, the clouds and bushes have the same artwork and are just different colors.",
      "correct_answer": "True",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "False"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Science & Nature",
      "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "Salt is 100% composed of Sodium.",
      "correct_answer": "False",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "True"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Politics",
      "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "Donald Trump won the popular vote in the 2016 United States presidential election.",
      "correct_answer": "False",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "True"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "History",
      "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "Kublai Khan is the grandchild of Genghis Khan?",
      "correct_answer": "True",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "False"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
      "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "In the &quot;S.T.A.L.K.E.R.&quot; series, the Freedom faction wishes to destroy the supernatural area known as  &quot;the Zone&quot;.",
      "correct_answer": "False",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "True"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Science: Mathematics",
      "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "An equilateral triangle always has every angle measuring 60&deg;.",
      "correct_answer": "True",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "False"
      ]
    }
  ]
